Have you ever heard the term insurable interest
in life insurance?  These are the
basic things you need to know before
having life insurance.  Without this,
your policy may become invalid.  So,
insurable interest is a basic principle
in life insurance which states
that you have a legitimate financial interest
[music] or family relationship
in accordance with the provisions in force in
Indonesia.  The relationship in question is
between the policy holder, insured,
heir, or premium payer.  For example,
husband and wife [music]
or parents and children.
So, are office friends or girlfriends
considered insurable interests or not?
[music] Not included, huh?  Insurable
interest is important to prevent
insurance abuse and is in line
with the main purpose of insurance,
namely protection from risks related to
life and health.
Yeah.